<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="addendum_id_print">
            <t t-call="web.html_container">
                <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                    <t t-call="web.basic_layout">
                        <div class="page">
                            <h4 class="text-center">ADDENDUM TO TENANCY CONTRACT (DMCC NO ASP7096)</h4>
                            <table class="table table-sm table-borderless">
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Payments
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        1.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant will pay the Rent on the due dates specified in the Rent Payment Plan
                                        and according to the terms of this Tenancy
                                        Contract whether formally demanded or not, without exception, deduction,
                                        set-off, counterclaim or retention of any kind.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Security Deposit
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        2.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        A security Deposit equivalent to 10% (AED 30,000) of the Year 1 rent is payable
                                        to the Landlord at the time of signing this
                                        Tenancy Contract.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        3.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Should the Landlord not deduct any amount from the Security Deposit, then the
                                        Landlord shall refund the Security Deposit to the
                                        Tenant in sixty (60) days after the expiry or termination of this Tenancy
                                        Contract and after receiving a written request from the
                                        Tenant accompanied by the Handover Form.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Taxes, fees and costs
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        4.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        If the Landlord is registered for Value Added Tax (VAT), then VAT shall be paid
                                        by the Tenant on the rent. The Landlord will be
                                        required to produce a Tax Registration Number and TRN certificate.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        5.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        If a Tenant’s cheque is dishonoured, then Tenant shall pay to the Landlord a fee
                                        of AED 1,000 plus AED 50 VAT.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        6.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        If the Tenant fails to make any due payment by the due date, the Landlord may
                                        charge a fee at a rate of 2% per month of the
                                        amount due until such payment due is made.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Handover
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        7.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Handover of the Premises to the Tenant shall occur once the Tenant has signed
                                        the tenancy contract and paid the security
                                        deposit and first rental instalment and provided post-dated cheques as per the
                                        Rent Payment Plan.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        8.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        It is the Landlord’s responsibility to ensure the unit is not registered under
                                        an existing Trade License (including own entities or
                                        previous Tenants) and has no existing liabilities, including but not limited to
                                        utilities, community service charges,
                                        telecommunications.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Utilities and charges
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        10.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant is responsible for payment of all electricity, water, cooling and gas
                                        charges resulting from occupying the property.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        11.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant is responsible for payment of telecommunications resulting from
                                        occupying the property.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        12.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Owner is responsible for payment of community service charges. Any utility
                                        services billed via service charges but that
                                        relate to the property and that due to a lack of individual premise metering are
                                        charged to the Landlord, shall be reimbursed by
                                        Tenant within 30 days subject to receiving an invoice from the Owner.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Parking
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        13.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        There is two (2) parking space included. Parking slots B3-02/03 as per Title
                                        Deed.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Permitted use
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        14.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant shall use the Premises only for the permitted use as per activities
                                        allowed under their Commercial License
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        15.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant shall pay AED 250 to register the tenancy contract via Ejari.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        16.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Landlord shall provide documents if required for Ejari or required by DMCC.
                                        The Landlord shall not withhold any documents
                                        to prevent the Tenant from applying for their DMCC license.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Fitting out and alteration
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        17.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant may not make modifications to the Premises or alter the fit-out
                                        without a letter of no objection from the Landlord. The
                                        Tenant agrees to provide the as-built, Concordia approved drawings to the
                                        Landlord on completion of the modifications.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Care and maintenance
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        18.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant is responsible for the maintenance and upkeep of fixtures, fittings,
                                        and mechanical, electrical and plumbing
                                        components of the Premises.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        19.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The repair or replacement of an item or part costing more than of AED 1,000
                                        shall be the responsibility of the Landlord to pay
                                        and the repair and replacement of an item or part costing AED 1,000 or less
                                        shall be the responsibility of the Tenant to pay.
                                        The Tenant shall be responsible for call out charges as applicable incurred by
                                        the landlord if the repair cost is assessed to be
                                        under AED 1,000.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Access and inspection
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        20.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant agrees to provide access to service providers authorised by the
                                        Landlord at all reasonable times and with two
                                        business days’ notice to inspect, maintain, repair, or improve the property.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        21.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant agrees to allow the property to be viewed during the last three
                                        months of the Tenancy Contract term or its earlier
                                        termination at all reasonable times by brokers and prospective purchasers or
                                        tenants of the property authorised by the
                                        Landlord
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Insurance and indemnity
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        22.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Insurance of the contents of the property is the responsibility of the Tenant.
                                        The Tenant indemnifies the Landlord If the Tenant
                                        does not insure the contents of the property and suffers loss or damage on
                                        account of fire, theft, flood or accident or for any
                                        such event to the property during the Tenancy period.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Renewal
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        23.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Three (3) months’ notice in writing will be given to the Landlord if the tenant
                                        does not wish to renew the tenancy contract.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Vacating
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        24.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant shall provide the Landlord with copies of all final utility bills and
                                        evidence of payment thereof upon vacating the property.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        25.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant agrees that any rent, costs, or fees payable to the Landlord that
                                        have not been paid by the Tenant by the end of
                                        the Tenancy Contract term will be deducted from the Security Deposit.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        26.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        At the end of the Tenancy Contract term or its earlier termination, the Tenant
                                        must provide the Landlord with proof of an
                                        address change from DMCC or a final de registration received from DMCC before
                                        the security deposit is returned to the
                                        Tenant.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        27.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        The Tenant will hand back the unit in the same condition as it was received and
                                        will repair any damages (excluding fair wear and
                                        tear) to the premises or any of the Landlord's fitting and fixtures on vacating
                                        the premises.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        28.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Tenant improvements to the Premises may be left in place at the discretion of
                                        the Landlord.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Termination
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        29.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Should the Tenant wish to break the lease during the Tenancy Contract term, the
                                        Landlord will require three (3) months’ written
                                        notice and a penalty of equivalent 3 months’ rent to be paid by the Tenant.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th colspan="2">
                                        Force Majeure
                                    </th>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        30.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Neither Party shall be held responsible for any delay in performance of any of
                                        its obligations under this Agreement (except
                                        accrued payment obligations) where such delay in performance is because of an
                                        event of Force Majeure.
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                                <tr>
                                    <th width="5%">
                                        31.
                                    </th>
                                    <td>
                                        Force Majeure means a circumstance, condition or event outside the reasonable
                                        direct or indirect control of the Party affected,
                                        but only to the extent that such circumstances, condition or event:
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                            </table>
                        </div>
                    </t>
                </t>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>